Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts, 1928-1958
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- 16mm As-Broadcast Microfilm, 1928-1958
  - Penick & Ford
    - Vermont Maid syrup
      - Vermont Lumberjacks, coastal stations, 1931 Jan.-1932 Mar.
      - Spots and recordings, 1937-1938
    - Br'er Rabbit molasses
      - Ida Bailey Allen, 1930 Sept.-1931 Mar.
      - Ida Bailey Allen, coastal stations, 1930 Sept.-1931 Mar.
    - Br'er Rabbit syrup
      - Spot announcements, 1934 Oct.4
    - Br'er Rabbit molasses
      - Spot announcements, 1935
    - Br'er Rabbit gingerbread flour
      - Spot announcements, 1937
    - Br'er Rabbit molasses
      - Spot announcements, 1937
      - Spot announcements, live, 1937
      - Spot announcements, live and recorded, 1938
  - Libby McNeil & Libby
    - Around the World with Libby, 1929 June-1930 June
    - The Libby Grocer, 1930 Sept.-Dec.
    - Ray Perkins, 1930 Oct.-1931 Mar.
    - Ray Perkins, 1931 Apr.-Dec. (Reel 156)
  - Kellogg Co.
    - The Circle, 1939 Jan.-July
      [See reel 48 dramatic script for Mar. 26 and Apr. 2 broadcasts]
    - Howie Wing, A Saga of Aviation, WABC, 1938 Oct.
      [First 10 episodes; agency was N.W. Ayer]
    - Howie Wing, A Saga of Aviation, WABC, 1938 Nov.-1939 May (Reel 157)
    - Howie Wing, A Saga of Aviation, WABC, 1939 May-June (Reel 158)
  - Lamont-Corliss (Pond's creams)
    - Commercials, 1933 Jan.-July
      [Mrs. Roosevelt through Mar. 3]
    - Commercials, 1933 Aug.-1934 Jan.
    - Commercials, Maude Adams, 1934 Jan.-Mar.
      [Feb. 16 and 23 missing]
    - Commercials, Mrs. Roosevelt, 1937 Apr.-July
    - Husbands and Wives, 1936 Aug.-Dec.
    - Husbands and Wives, 1937 (Reel 159)
  - Danya
    - Commercials, testimonials, 1937-1939
  - Seeck & Kade (Pertussin)
    - Pertussin Play Boys, 1930 Dec.-1931 Apr.
    - Frank Strutz & Orchestra, 1931 Dec.-1932 Jan.
    - Spot announcements, 1938, 1940
  - Standard Brands (Reel 165)
    - Tenderleaf tea
      - One Man's Family, 1935 Mar.-1936 June
      - One Man's Family, 1936 June-Dec., 1940 Jan.-July (Reel 166)
      - One Man's Family, 1940 Aug.-Dec. (Reel 167)
    - Fleischmann's yeast drink, Canadian commercials, 1940 Oct.-Nov., 1941 Jan.-July
    - Royal tapioca pudding, Commercials, 1940 Nov.-1941 Jan.
    - Royal baking powder
      - Commercials, 1941 Feb.
      - One Man's Family, 1941 Jan.-July
    - Royal Gelatin, 1941 June
    - Tenderleaf tea (Reel 168)
      - One Man's Family, 1941 July-Dec.
    - Royal tapioca pudding, commercials, 1941 Aug.
    - Fleischmann's yeast, commercials, 1941 July-Aug.
    - Tenderleaf tea
      - One Man's Family, script, 1942 Jan.-July
      - commercials, 1942 Sept. 6
    - Royal desserts
      - One Man's Family, 1942 July-Aug.
    - Fleischmann's yeast, commercials, 1942 Jan.-May
    - Royal puddings, commercials, 1942 Apr.-Sept.
    - Tenderleaf tea, 1942 July-Aug.
    - Royal Gelatin, pudding, script, 1942 July-Aug.
    - Tenderleaf tea
      - Canada, Vass Family, 1940 Nov. 26
      - I Love a Mystery, 1941 Sept. 22
      - Canada, 1941 Jan. 17
      - One Man's Family, Sales Meeting record, 1941 Aug. 27
      - Great Falls, Mont., one-minute announcement, 1941 Oct. 14
      - Canada, Vass Family, 1941 Jan. 7
  - Wm. Wrigley, Jr. (Reel 169)
    - Doublemint Gum, commercials, 1939 Dec.-1942 Apr.
    - Gene Autry program (Melody Ranch), 1942 Apr.-Dec. (Reel 170)
  - Warner Bros.
    - Out of the Fog, scripts and commercials, 1941 May
    - Sergeant York, commercials, 1941 June-Aug.
  - U.S. Playing Card Co.
    - Scripts and commercials, 1941 Oct. 24
    - Commercials, 1941 Nov.-1942 Jan.
  - Lamont-Corliss (Danya)
    - Commercials, 1940 Oct.-1941 Nov.
  - Groves (Bromo-Quinine)
    - Commercials, 1941 Oct.-Nov.
  - Committee to Defend Americans By Aiding the Allies
    - Spot announcements, 1941 Jan. 23
  - Cosmopolitan magazine
    - Commercials, 1941 Feb. 27
  - Penick & Ford
    - Br'er Rabbit molasses, commercials, 1941 Feb.-Oct.
  - City Baking Co. (Rice Bakeries)
    - Commercials, 1941 Apr.
  - Alice Bailey's Desserts (Kraft)
    - Commercials, 1941 Mar.-Apr.
  - Fanny Farmer Candies
    - Commercials, 1942 July-Sept.
      [See reel 201 for Nov.-Dec. 1942]
  - Auditions
    - Libby McNeil & Libby, 1941 May 18
    - N.Y. State Assn. of Architects, So You're Going to Build, 1941 Apr. 17
    - Philco, John Doe American, 1941 Dec. 15
    - Ward's Tip Top Bread
      - Phil Cook Show, 1941 Nov. 18
      - The Secret Three, 1941 Dec. 30
    - American magazine, American Scene, 1935 July 8
    - Bromo-Seltzer (Emerson Drug), 1935 June 3
    - White Owl cigars (General Cigar), 1935
    - Cutex (Northam Warren), 1935
    - American Tobacco (Half & Half), 1935
    - Johns-Manville, You Can Be Successful, 1935
    - Elgin, 1935
    - Elgin, Dale Carnegie, 1941
    - Shell, 1935, 1937
    - Royal Gelatin (Standard Brands)
      - Jeeves, 1934 July 24
      - Wodehouse, memo, 1939 Aug. 2
    - Planter's Cocktail Peanuts, 1939 Dec.
  - U.s. Marines
    - Commercials, 1941 Dec.
  - Guinness Stout
    - Commercials, 1941 Jan.
  - Magic Baking Powder (Canada)
    - Commercials, 1941 Dec. 26
  - Fleischmann's Yeast (Canada)
    - Commercials, 1942 Jan. 6
  - Kellogg Co.
    - Corn Flakes, commercials, Latin America, 1941 July 30
  - Martini & Rossi (vermouth) (Reel 171)
    - Commercials, 1941 May-June
  - General Electric
    - Radio program, 1941
  - Block Drug Co.
    - Dentu-Grip, commercials, 1942 June-July
    - Gold Medal capsules, commercials, 1942 July-Dec.
  - Brater's Powder
    - Commercials, 1940 Sept.
  - Bromo-Seltzer (Emerson Drug)
    - Commercials, 1939 Nov.-1940 Feb.
  - Auditions
    - Crossroads USA
      - Bromo-Seltzer (Emerson Drug), 1940 July 19
      - Schick razor, 1940 July 19
      - Gillette blades, 1940 Aug. 8
      - Wrigley Doublemint gum, 1940 July 23
      - Bab-O, 1940 Aug. 9
      - Sealtest Ice Cream (Sheffield), 1940 Aug. 8
      - American Dairy Association, 1940 July 17
      - Old Gold cigarettes (Lorillard), 1940 July 19
      - Kellogg's Corn Flakes, 1940 July 19
      - Script (no commercials or clients), 1940 Dec. 7
    - Marionette Show, Charlie McCarthy, Worlds Fair, 1940
      [By Sue Hastings]
    - Shell Television,1940 Dec.
    - Planter's Peanuts
      - Name It and Claim It, 1940 Nov. 26
      - Script (no commercials or clients), 1940 Dec.
    - Script (no client), Soldier from the Wars Returning, 1940
    - Absorbine Jr. (Young)Meet Your Voice, 1940 Nov. 28
    - Script (no client), Race of Hearts, 1940
    - Old Gold cigarettes (Lorillard), Strictly G.I., 1940 Dec. 19
    - Eastman Kodak
      - Musical Pictures, 1942 Sept. 13
      - Lifebuoy, 1942 Aug. 28
      - Aetna Life Affiliated Companies, 1942 Aug.-Sept.
      - Pennsylvania Anthracite, 1942 Jan. 6
    - Lever Brothers
      - John Doe American, 1942 Mar.
      - Life and Love of Dr. Susan, 1939 Jan.-Feb.
        [Episodes 1, 2, 210]
    - Lever Brothers (Lux)
      - Family Man, 1939 Jan. 9
      - Wayne King and Frank Luther, undated
      - Lux Radio Fiction Club, 1939
      - All This and Heaven Too, 1939
        [Episodes 1, 5]
    - White Owl cigars, Who-Who, 1939 May 29
  - Advance program announcement
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1941 Aug. 27
    - White Owl cigars, 1941 Aug. 26
    - Ballantine Three Ring Time, 1941 Aug., Nov.
    - True or False, 1941 June-Dec.
    - Chase & Sanborn Coffee, 1941 Aug., Dec.
    - Old Gold cigarettes (Lorillard), 1941 Jan.-Apr.
    - Columbia Network, 1941 Aug. 212
    - Johns-Manville
      - Frazier Hunt, 1941 Oct. 10
      - De Mille, 1941 Aug. 22
  - N.Y. State Republican Committee
    - Commercials, 1941 Oct. 10
  - Royal Gelatin
    - Commercials, Montana, 1941 Oct.
  - Rice's Homemade Bread
    - Vass Family, 1941 Apr. 25
  - Lamont-Corliss (Pond's)
    - Commercials, 1941 Feb.-Mar.
  - People's Drug Co.
    - Commercials, 1941 Feb.
  - Planter's Peanuts
    - Commercials, 1940 Oct.-1941 Jan.
    - Script, 1941 Feb. 5
    - Peanut Oil and Magic Mixer, audition, 1941 May
    - Planter's Cocktail Peanuts, 1941 Oct.-Dec.
    - American Institute of Food Products, 1941 Aug.-Dec.
  - British-American Oil
    - Band Wagon (Toronto office), 1942 Feb.
  - Penick & Ford
    - Br'er Rabbit molasses, commercials, 1942 Aug.24
    - Br'er Rabbit syrup, commercials, 1942 July 31
    - Legal and client OK's, 1942
  - Advance program announcement
    - Ward's Tip Top Bread, Terry and the Pirates, 1942 Apr. 21
    - White Owl cigars, 1942 Dec. 8
    - Chase & Sanborn
      - Coffee, 1942 Aug. 31
      - One Man's Family, 1942 Aug. 31
    - Old Gold cigarettes (Lorillard), 1942 Jan.-Apr.
  - Universal Pictures
    - Hellzapoppin, commercials, 1941 Dec.-1942 Jan.
  - Lamont-Corliss (Pond's)
    - Commercials, 1942 Jan.-Sept.
  - Shell Oil
    - Commercials, 1942 Mar. 13
      [30-second spots]
  - Penick Starch
    - Commercials, 1942 Apr. 29
  - Planter's Peanuts
    - American Institute of Food Products, commercials, 1942 Jan.-Mar.
    - Commercials, 1942 Jan.-Aug.
    - Commercials, 1942 July-Dec. (Reel 172)
    - Commercials, 1940-1943 (Reel 173)
    - Commercials, Vacuum can, 1941 Jan. 2
  - Seeck & Kade (Pertussin)
    - Spot announcements, 1940 July 11
  - City Baking Co. (Rice Bakeries)
    - Commercials, Washington and Baltimore, 1940 Jan.-Oct.
    - Rice's School Lunch Loaf, 1940 Feb., Sept.
    - Commercials, 1939 Sept.-1940 Sept.
  - Johns-Manville Co.
    - Commercials, WGY, 1940 Apr.-July
    - Commercials, WMCA, 1940 Aug.
    - News, Frazier Hunt, 1941 Sept.-Dec.
    - News, Elma Davis, 1942 Jan.-June
      [Feb. 12 missing; see reel 174]
    - News, Cecil Brown, 1942 June-July
    - News, Cecil Brown, 1942 July-Dec. (Reel 174)
  - Sherwin-Williams
    - Metropolitan Opera, audition, 1940 Mar. 17
  - Calsodent
    - Bob Howard, 1940 Jan.-Apr.
  - Northam Warren
    - Cutex, commercials, 1939 Oct.-Dec.
    - Odorono, spot announcements, 1942 Oct.
  - Proposal for Government Messages on Commercial Network Programs, 1940 Feb. 23
  - Mentholatum
    - Barn Dance, spot announcements, 1942 Sept. 26
  - Eastman Kodak
    - Musical Pictures, 1942 Nov.
  - Lamont-Corliss (Danya)
    - Spot announcements, 1940 Sept.-Dec.
  - California Wines
    - Commercials, 1940 Oct.
      [In Italian, with translations]
  - Groves (Bromo-Quinine)
    - Commercials, 1940 Sept.-1941 Jan.
    - Spot announcements, 1940 Sept.-Dec. (Reel 175)
  - Kellogg Co.
    - Commercials, 1942
      [In Spanish]
  - Ward Baking Co.
    - Phil Cook Show, Comics, audition, 1941
    - Commercials, 1941 Sept.-1942 Sept.
  - Johns-Manville Co.
    - Audition, 1941 Dec. 23
  - General Cigar (White Owl)
    - Fred H. Ferrar (trumpet), 1939 Apr. 13
    - Raymond Grave Swing, 1939 Sept.-Dec.
    - World's Fair exhibit building recording, 1940 May 2
    - Spot announcements, 1940 Apr. 15
    - Raymond Grave Swing, 1940 Jan.-Aug.
      [No broadcast Jan. 8; missing May 15, June 24-26 broadcasts]
    - Raymond Grave Swing, 1940 Aug.-Dec. (Reel 176)
    - Hendrick Van Loon, 1940 Dec. 27-1941 Jan. 10
    - Raymond Grave Swing, 1941-1942
  - Kraft Cheese (Reel 177)
    - Kraft Music Hall, Bing Crosby, etc., 1940 Jan.-1941 Jan.
      [No broadcast June 27 due to Republican Convention]
    - Kraft Music Hall, Bing Crosby, etc., 1941 Jan.-1942 Feb. (Reel 178)
      [Missing Feb. 5 1942 broadcast; July and August 1941 broadcasts are on reel 214]
    - Kraft Music Hall, Bing Crosby, etc., 1942 Jan.-Dec. (Reel 179)
      [Dec. 3 broadcast on reel 214]
  - Sterno Canned Heat
    - Spot announcements, 1941 Dec. 23
  - U.S. Playing Card Co.
    - Commercials, 1940 Nov.
  - Scott Paper Co.
    - Scott Towels, commercials, 1941 Sept.
    - Scott Towels, commercials, 1940 Mar.-May, 1941 Oct.-Dec. (Reel 180)
  - Shell Oil
    - Commercials, 1940 Apr.-May, Aug.-Sept.
    - Scripts, 1940
    - Shell Information Show, Five Dollar Fact, 19490 July-Sept.
    - Audition, 1940 Oct. 28
    - Shell Information Show, Five Dollar Fact, 1941 Apr.-Aug.
    - Shell Information Show, Five Dollar Fact, 1941 Aug. (Reel 181)
    - Shell Comes to the Party, 1941 Aug.
    - X-100, commercials, 1941 May-June
    - Shellane, commercials, 1941 May-Aug.
    - Shell gasoline and motor oil, commercials, 1941 Apr.
    - Shell Premium, spot announcements, 1941 July
    - Shell Thermo-Fast Service, commercials, 1941 Sept.
    - One minute spot announcements,1941 Sept.-Oct.
    - Shell Winterizing, commercials, 1941 Oct.
    - Shell Football Show, commercials, 1941 Oct.-Nov.
    - Shell Pigskin Parade, commercials, 1941 Sept.-Nov.
    - Miscellaneous, commercials, 1941
    - Shell Bugle spots, commercials, 1940 Sept., 1941 Apr.
    - Shellane, commercials, 1941 Mar. 26
    - Shell Oil jingles, 1941 Apr. 1
    - X-100, Speaking of Speed, commercials, 1941 apr. 26
  - J.B. Williams
    - Williams shaving cream, True Or False program, Dr. Harry Hagen, 1940 Jan.-1942 Nov.
      [No broadcasts in summer]
    - Williams shaving cream, True Or False program, Dr. Harry Hagen, 1942 Nov.-Dec.
    - Glider, Wm. Cunningham Participation program, commercials, 1940
    - Pearson & Allen, Washington Merry Go-Round, 1940 July-Sept.
    - Ted Steele, Gliding Swing program, 1940 Jan.-July
    - WTIC, Williams News Program, 1940-1941 Sept.
    - WQXR, Williams News Program, 1940-1942
    - Williams shaving cream, WFIL commercials, 1941 Sept. 16
    - Williams shaving cream, True Or False program, Dr. Harry Hagen, 1942 Nov.-Dec. (Reel 182)
    - Glider, Wm. Cunningham Participation program, commercials, 1940
      [Gift cake of Lanoline soap]
    - Pearson & Allen, Washington Merry Go-Round, 1940 July-Sept.
    - Ted Steele, Gliding Swing program, 1940 Jan.-July
    - WTIC, Williams News Program, 1940 Jan.-1941 Sept.
      [Rota-Shaver, Aqua Velva, Glider]
    - WQXR, Williams News Program, 1940 Feb.-Aug., 1942 Feb.-Aug.
    - Williams shaving cream, WFIL commercials, 1941 Sept. 16
    - Glider, Walgreen Drug, commercials, 1941 Jan.-Apr.
      [WIND, WENR, WGN]
    - WQXR, Williams News Program, commercials, 1940 Jan.-July
    - Aqua Velva, spot announcements, 1940 July-Aug., 1941 Jan.-Sept.
    - WTIC, Williams News Program, commercials, 1940 May 1-2
    - Latin American program, commercials, 1940 Aug.-1941 July
  - W.F. Young, Inc. (Absorbine Jr.)
    - True Or False program, Dr. Harry Hagen, 1941 July-Sept.
  - Luden's Cough Drops
    - Commercials, 1940 Nov. 29
  - Lever Brothers (Lux)
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1940 Jan.
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1940 Jan.-Oct. (Reel 183)
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1941 Oct.-July (Reel 184)
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1941 Sept.-1942 Apr. (Reel 185)
      [No summer broadcasts; Act III of Lady Eve, Mar. 9, 1942, missing due to President's talk]
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1942 Apr.-Dec. (Reel 186)
    - Lux Flakes, Spot announcements, 1941 Mar.-June, 1942 Feb.
    - Lux Toilet Soap, Spot announcements, 1941 Mar.-Dec., 1942 Feb.
  - Old Gold Cigarettes (Lorillard) (Reel 187)
    - Benny Goodman, What's New?, 1941 Feb.-May
    - Herbert Marshall, 1941 Nov.-Dec.
    - Tommy Riggs, 1941 Apr.-Oct.
    - Four Corners USA, 1941 Feb.-Aug.
    - Auditions (Reel 188)
      - Crossroads USA, 1941 Feb. 4
      - Girls Trio, 1941 Feb. 3
      - Benny Goodman, undated
    - New program announcement, Four Corners USA, 1941 Feb. 4
    - Richard Rollmand and Gracie Benrie, Spot announcements, 1940 Dec.-1941 Nov.
    - WTAG, commercials, 1940 Dec.-1941 June
    - Benny Goodman, new program announcement, 1941 Feb. 6
    - Commercials, 1941 Feb. 10
    - Chicago WENR, 1-12, 1941 Jan. 9
    - New York WABC, 1-10, 1941 Mar.
    - New York WEAF, 1-10, 1941 Mar. 19
    - New York WEAF, A-M, 1941 June 30
    - New York WQXR, 1941 Jan. and July
    - Columbus, Oh. WHKC, 1940 Dec.-1941 Mar.
    - Detroit WJR
      - Good Morning in Music, 1941 Oct.-Dec.
      - Old Gold Sports Review with Tommy Harmon, 1941 Oct.-Dec.
    - Philadelphia WFIL, 1940 Dec. 27
    - Washington WINX, 1941 Oct. 16
    - Spot announcements, 1941 Nov.-Dec.
    - New York WHN, 1940 Dec.-1941 Oct.
    - Miami WKAT, 1941 Dec. 26
    - New York WHN, 1941
    - Yankee Network and WHN, Spot announcements, B1-B12, 1942 Jan. 26
    - WHN, Brooklyn baseball play by play, 1942 Mar.-Aug.
      [See reel 210 for Mar. 12 broadcast]
    - WHN, Brooklyn baseball play by play, 1942 Aug.-Sept. (Reel 189)
    - WHN, N.Y. Giants football play by play, 1942 Oct.-Dec.
      [See also reels 210, 212, 214]
    - Commercials, 1942 Apr.-Dec.
    - KOA, 1942 Oct.-Nov.
      - Old Gold Sports Review with Tommy Harmon, 1942 Jan.-Mar.
      - Sports Roundup WISH, 1942 Oct.-1943 Jan.
    - Commercials, WGN Bob Elson, 1941 Jan.-Aug.
      [Muriel, Van Bibber cigars, Friends pipe tobacco also mentioned in scripts]
    - WGN Bob Elson, Baseball play by play, 1941 Apr. 8
    - WGN Bob Elson, Baseball play by play, 1941 Aug.-Sept. (Reel 190)
      [Muriel cigars mentioned in scripts]
    - WGN, An Hour with Elsond Anson, 1941 Oct.
    - WGN Bob Elson, Old Gold Show, 1941 Oct.-1942 Apr.
      [Van Bibber cigars, Friends pipe tobacco mentioned in Aug. 1 script.]
    - WGN (Reel 191)
      - Baseball play by play, 1942 Sept.
      - Baseball play by play, 1943 Apr.-Aug.
    - WHN, WGN, WOL, WWDC, Baseball play by play, 1943 Aug.-Oct. (Reel 192)
    - Commercials, 1943 Jan.
    - Red Barber
      - Old Gold program, commercials, 1943 Jan.-Aug.
      - Old Gold Record of the Day, commercials, 1943 Feb.-Mar.
        [See reel 211 for rest]
      - Old Gold Sports News with Bill Stern, commercials, 1943 Jan.-Aug.
        [See reel 210 for Oct. 26, 1943 through Jan. 15, 1943, and Aug. 20-Oct. 22, 1943]
      - Old Gold Campus News, commercials, 1943 Jan.-Mar.
      - Old Gold Gloom Dodgers, commercials, 1943 Jan.-Apr.
      - Old Gold/Fulton Lewis, commercials, 1943 Jan.-Sept.
        [See also reel 211]
      - Old Gold/Vadeboncoeur, commercials, 1943 Jan.-Sept.
      - Old Gold Sports Roundup, commercials, 1943 Jan.-Sept.
      - Herbert Marshall, commercials, 1942 Apr.
  - Penick & Ford
    - Br'er Rabbit molasses
      - Marjorie Mills Participation program, 1941-1943
        [Mr. Seaburgh's files]
      - Martha Brooks, WGY Market Basket, 1938-1943
      - Agnes White, KFI, California Home, 1941-1943
  - Scott Paper Co.
    - Scott Towels
      - Listen Ladies, undated
      - Round Robin Review, 1941 Sept.-Nov.
      - Dollars and Sense,1941 Dec.
      - Special announcements, CNL, 1941 Sept.-Oct.
      - Home Forum, KDKA, 1941 Sept.-Nov.
      - Charmingly We Live, KEX, 1941 Oct.-Nov.
  - P. Ballantine & Sons (Reel 199)
    [See also reels 133, 171]
    - Special dealer record, 1940 Sept. 18
    - Spot announcements, 1940 July-Nov.
    - Merchandising record,1941 Jan. 27
    - Spot announcements, Ted Steele, 1941 Jan.-Feb.
    - Spot announcements, Ale, 1941 Apr.-July
    - Spot announcements, Beer, 1941 May 7
    - Spot announcements, Ale and beer for Puerto Rico, 1941 June 4
    - Three Ring Time, Bob Crosby, Chas. Laughton, Milton Berle, etc.1941 Sept.-1942 June
    - Three Ring Round Up, commercials, 1942 June-Oct.
    - Three Ring Round Up, scripts, 1942 Sept.-Oct.
    - Ballantine Ale, quart bottle, Spot announcements, 1-10 over WCAX, 1942 June
    - Three Ring Time, Guy Lombardi and Ogden Nash, 1943 Mar.-Sept.
    - Three Ring Time, Guy Lombardi and Ogden Nash, 1943 Sept.-Dec. (Reel 200)
    - Three Ring Time, Guy Lombardi and Ogden Nash, spot announcements, 1943 Feb.-Sept.
  - Radio Corporation of America (RCA)
    - What's New, Lou Bring, etc., 1943 Sept.-Dec.
  - Mr. Seaburgh's file
    - Scott Towels, commercials, KFSD, 1941 Oct.
    - Scott Towels, commercials, KMOX, 1941 Dec.
    - Scott Towels, Homekeeper's Calendar, KOMO, 1941 Oct.-Dec.
    - Scott Towels, commercials, KPRC, 1941? Dec.
      [And Yankees Network, WBAL, WBAP, KGKO, WBT, WCAD, WFLA, WGAR, WGY, WJAX, WJR, WJZ, WLS, WLW, WSYR, WWL, WIDD]
  - Lever Brothers (Lux)
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1943 Jan.-May
      [See also reels 31, 35, 102-110, 134-137, 153, 171, 182]
    - Lux Radio Theatre, 1943 May-July, Sept.-Dec. (Reel 201)
      [Nov. 8 broadcast missing]
    - Lux test commercials,1943 June 23
    - Aunt Jenny Hitchhikes, 1943 July-Aug.
  - United Nations Information Bureau
    - Eight Legal Governments of Invaded Europe: What They Are Doing To Defeat Hitler and Establish Peace, 1943
    - Norway, 1943
    - Yugoslavia, 1943
  - United Churches Canvass/U.S. Marine Corps
    - Major Gen. Alexander Archer Vandergrift, 1943 Mar. 12
  - Auditions
    - Writers' War Board, Good Company, 1943
    - You And Your Dog (Defense Dog), 1943
  - W.F. Young, Inc. (Absorbine Jr.)
    - Spot announcements, 1943 Mar.-June
  - Anacin Mfg. Co.
    - Army and Navy award program, Life for the Wounded, 1943 Mar. 24
  - Bank of America
    - California Carry On, 1943 Sept.-Dec.
  - Wartime Conference
    - Boys Clubs of America, Herbert Hoover, Lt. Gen. Thomas Holcomb, USMC, 1943 May
  - Fanny Farmer Candies
    - Spot announcements, 1942 Nov.-Dec.
      [See also reel 170]
  - Lamont-Corliss (Pond's creams)
    - Spot announcements, 1943 Jan.-Sept.
  - Universal Pictures
    - Flesh and Fantasy, commercials, 1943 Oct.
      [See also reels 33, 171]
  - Superin (Carter Products)
    - Spot announcements, 1943 June-Dec.
    - Keepsakes, 1943 Sept. 19
    - Keepsakes, 1943 Sept. 19 (Reel 202)
  - Shell Oil
    - Shell Ground Crew Service, spot announcements, 1942 Mar. 13
    - Sunset Valley Barn Dance, commercials, 1942 Apr.-July
    - Spotlight on Sports, commercials, 1943 Oct.-Nov.
  - Planter's Peanuts
    [See also reels 170-173]
    - WRC peanuts, commercials, 1943 Nov.-Dec.
    - WTIC peanuts, commercials, 1943 Nov.-Dec.
    - WEAF peanut butter, commercials, 1943 Nov.-Dec.
  - Standard Brands
    - Chase & Sanborn
      [Includes Tenderleaf tea Sept. 1942-Dec. 1943; Stams May-Dec. 1943]
      - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1941
        [No broadcasts July-Aug.; see also reels 93-98]
      - Abbott & Costello, 1941 Apr.
      - Spot announcements, 1941, 1943
      - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1942 Jan.-May
      - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1942 May-Dec. (Reel 203)
        [No broadcasts July-Aug., or Dec. 27]
      - Don Ameche, 1942 Sept.-Dec.
      - Abbott & Costello, 1941 Apr.-June
      - E Award program, 1943 Jan.-Aug.
      - Paul Whiteman, 1943 June-Aug.
      - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1943 Sept.-Dec.
      - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy, 1943 Dec. (Reel 204)
    - Fleischmann Yeast, Bakers of America, 1943 Dec. 21
    - Mary Marlin
      - Audition script, 1943 Sept.
      - Tenderleaf Tea, 1943 Sept.-Dec.
      - Royal Gelatin/desserts, 1943 Sept.-Dec.
  - Woman Power
    - Dramatized spots, 1-12, 1943 Mar.
  - Brewing Industry Foundation
    - Maine spots 31-43, 1943 June 16
  - Kraft Cheese (Reel 205)
    - Kraft Music Hall, Bing Crosby, etc., 1943 Jan.-Aug.
      [Missing Nov.-Dec. 23--see reel 214 for missing broadcasts; missing July 1, 1943]
  - Owens Illinois Glass Co.
    - Homefront Matinee, 1943 Nov.-Dec.
      [Missing Nov. 15, 25, Dec. 15; Dec. 15 broadcast on reel 259]
  - Block Drug Co.
    - Gold Medal capsules, commercials, 1942 May-Aug.
    - Dentu-Grip commercials, 1942 Sept.-Nov.
    - Gold Medal capsules, Dentu-Grip, commercials, 1942 May
    - Gold Medal capsules, commercials, 1943 Jan.-Sept.
    - Dentu-Grip commercials, 1943 June-Nov.
    - Gold Medal capsules, Dentu-Grip, commercials, 1943 Mar. 25
    - Dentu-Grip commercials, 1944 Jan.-Apr.
    - Gold Medal capsules, commercials, 1944 Mar.-July
  - Groves (Bromo-Quinine)
    - Commercials, 1941 Oct.-1942 Jan.
  - Commercials, 1941 Oct.-1942 Jan. (Reel 206)
  - Johns-Manville Co.
    - News, Elma Davis, 1942 Feb. 12
      [See also reel 173]